The FBI has arrested almost 9,000 criminals in this year's crime sweep.
Illegal crossings along the border have plummeted to the lowest level since 1970.
Trump ran on keeping the borders and streets safe.
It's the reason he boosted his turnout with blacks.
For them to manipulate this now, to make it look like the troops are coming in to attack black people?
No.
They're coming in to do what we asked them to do.
And that is to get these illegals out of our communities.
Ribs is now going full tinfoil hat.
J.B. Beck says if they don't stop this N-word, he's going to steal the midterms.
I fear that what they're going to do is deploy these folks eventually to polling places
and say they're protecting the vote.
Do what he said he might do in 2020, which is use the military to confiscate the ballot boxes
and count the votes.
It's official.
New hoax alert.